Guide to the Jim Dow photographs, 1966-2019 RL.11709
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Negatives, 1966-2018; Original identifiers generally consist of the year taken and a two-digit number; after the 1970s the photographer's initials (jdd) preface all identifiers but are not expressed in this inventory. A few of the earliest identifiers may not always include the year, but others ha
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 1983; 60 folders (Box 17)
    Locations include: Islington, West Ham, Fainsburry, Scarborough and East Ham, London; Whitby; Eastbourne; Worthing; Manorlane; Leytonstone; Huddersfield; Bridlington; Holburn; Leeds; Ruston, North Yonks. Color.
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 1984; 12 folders (Box 17)
    Legacy identifiers: 1984-1102 to 1984-1114
    Locations include: Huddersfield; Halifax, West Yorkshire; London. Color.
  - Portugal, 2001; 3 folders (Box 18)
    Legacy identifiers: 2001-19 to 2001-42
    Location: Braga, Portugal. Color.
  - U.S. Road: Somerville, Massachusetts, 2002; 2 folders (Box 18)
    Legacy identifiers: 2002-92 to 2002-146
    Location: Somerville, MA. Color.
  - Argentina Stadiums, 1984; 23 folders (Box 19)
    Legacy identifiers: 1984-1035 to 1984-1047; many others with no identifiers
    Locations include: Buenos Aires; San Martin; Avellanada; Victoria; Mar Del Plata; Lomas de Zamora. Color.
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 1985; 41 folders (Box 20)
    Legacy identifiers: 1985-1119 to 1985-1169
    Locations include: Aldgate, Islington, Dalston, Tottenham, Kennington, Peckham, Forest Hill, Catford, and Bermondsey, London; North Yorkshire; Camden Town; Upper Norwood; Worcestershire; Wakefield, W. Yorks; Scarborough; Deptford; Camden Town; Greenwich. Color.
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 1986; 47 folders (Box 20)
    Legacy identifiers: 1986-1184 to 1986-1239
    Locations include: Cricklewood and Kings Cross, London; Manchester, Huddersfield and Oxford, England; Scarborough, Whitby and Ruston, North Yorkshire; Buxton, Derbyshire. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 1986; 26 folders (Box 21)
    Legacy identifiers: 1986-1241 to 1986-1263
    Locations include: Nueva Pompeya, Almagro, Colegiales, Barracas, Boca, Victoria, San Isidro and Rosthanera, Buenos Aires; Lujan. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 1987; 4 folders (Box 22)
    Legacy identifiers: jdd 1283-1335
    Locations include: Buenos Aires; Palermo. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 1988; 6 folders (Box 22)
    Legacy identifiers: jdd 1414-1530
    Locations include: Buenos Aires; Salta; Molinos; Quilmes, Tucuman Province; Córdoba, Province; Santa Fe Province; Temperley; Hipodromo; Lomas de Zamora; Mendoza Province; San Juan Province; San Luis. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 1987; 1 folder (Box 23)
    Legacy identifiers: 1987-1266 to 1987-1267
    Locations: Staunton and Crawford, VA. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 1988; 1 folder (Box 23)
    Legacy identifier: 1988-1345; others have no identifiers
    Locations: St. Paul, MN; Newton, PA. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 1989; 1 folder (Box 23)
    Legacy identifiers: 1989-1543 to 1989-1561
    Locations: Prattville, AL; Burlington, IA. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 1990; 1 folder (Box 23)
    Legacy identifiers: 1990-1611 to 1990-1613
    Locations: Boston and Provincetown, MA. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 1995; 2 folders (Box 23)
    Legacy identifiers: 95-13 to 95-57
    Locations include: Lamar, Doniphan, West Plains, Aurora, and Monett, MO; Partoville, Springdale, Fayetteville, Fort Smith, Hot Springs, Prescott, Hope, El Dorado, Malven, Arkadelphia, Dondarelle, Clarksville, Coal Hills, Bentonville, and Hoxie, AK; Fort Scott, KS; Woodhull, NY. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 1996; 1 folder (Box 23)
    Legacy identifiers: 1996-24 to 1996-25; 1996-50
    Locations: Woodhull, NY; Marineland, FL. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 1997; 1 folder (Box 23)
    Legacy identifier: 1997-80
    Location: Bath, NY. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 1998; 5 folders (Box 23)
    Legacy identifiers: 1998-1 to 1998-161
    Locations include: Wilson, Goldsboro, Lumberton, New Bern, Windsor, Halifax, Greenville, Ayden, Hookerton, Farmville and Norlina, NC; Allendale, and Levy, SC; East Dublin, Rex, Jackson, College Park, East Ellijay, Atlanta, Unadilla, Morae, and Savannah, GA; Phenix City, Bessemer, AL; Waterford, Oxford,and Clarksdale, MS; Chattanooga, and Elizabethtown, TN; Harrisonburg, Stephens City, Abingdon, Salida, Petersburg, and Fredericksburg, VA; Green Castle, York, Harrisonburg, Buchanan, Wytheville, Perkasie, and Wyoming, PA; Burlington, WV; Jackson, Holderness, Plymouth, and Ashland, NH; Concord and Somerville MA. Color.
  - U.S. / BBQ, 2000; 3 folders (Box 23)
    Legacy identifiers: 2000-03 to 2000-180
    Locations include: Norlina, Asheboro, Lexington, Salisbury, China Grove, Statesville, Mocksville, Cooleemee, and High Point, NC; Martinville, Danville, Lynchburg, and Richmond, VA; Putney, VT; Plymouth, NH; New Bedford, MA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1988; 29 folders (Box 24)
    Legacy identifiers: 1988-1377 to 1988-1413
    Cedar Rapids, Des Moines, Waterloo, Burlington, Davenport, amd Clinton, IA; Peoria, and Springfield, IL; Indianapolis, IN; Toledo, OH; Erie, PA; Glen Falls, NY; Pawtucket, RI. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1989; 25 folders (Box 24)
    Legacy identifiers: 1989-1559 to 1989-1567
    Omaha, NE; Augusta, Savannah, and Columbus, GA; Birmingham, AL; El Paso, TX; Oklahoma City, OK; Wichita, KS; Niagara Falls, and Batavia, NY; Omaha, NE; Burlington, IA; Appleton, Wausau, WI. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1990; 12 folders (Box 24)
    Legacy identifiers: 1990-1614 to 1990-1627
    Salt Lake City, UT; Butte, Great Falls, and Billings, MT; Idaho Falls, ID. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 1989; 4 folders (Box 25)
    Legacy identifiers: 1989-1568 to 1989-1610
    Location Include: Arrecipes and Belgrano, Buenos Aires; Lomas de Zamora; Temperley; Cordoba Province; Entre Rios Province; Villa Rosa. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 1990; 3 folders (Box 25)
    Legacy identifiers: 1990-1646 to 1990-1740
    Locations include: Hurlingham, Belgrano, Los Flores, Balcare, Los Matanza, and Tandil, Buenos Aires; Santa Domingo Lobos; Dolores; Ayacucho. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 1997; 4 folders (Box 25)
    Legacy identifiers: 1997-12 to 1997-79
    Locations include: San Isidro, and Barracas, Buenos Aires; Santa Fe Province; Entre Rios Province; Corrientes Province. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 1999; 3 folders (Box 25)
    Legacy identifiers: 1999-01 to 1999-63
    Locations include: Villa Devoto, Mataderos, San Telmo, Parque Centenario, Palermo, Villa Lupo, Moron, Villa Flores, Azul, Chillar, Del Areco, Pompeya, Congreso, Chacatia, and Munro, Recoleta Buenos Aires. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 2000; 3 folders (Box 25)
    Legacy identifiers: 2000-31 to 2000-84
    Location: Buenos Aires. Color.
  - UK: Non-Stadiums, 1990; 2 folders (Box 26)
    Legacy identifiers: 1990-1746 to 1990-1781
    Locations include: Derby; Derbyshire; Nottingham; London; North Yorks. Color.
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 1993; 3 folders (Box 26)
    Legacy identifiers: 1993-49 to 1993-80
    Locations include: East Ham, Southwark, Peckham, Soho, Bethnal Green, Islington, Spitalfields, and Moorgate, London; Lowestoft, Sussex. Color.
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 1994; 3 folders (Box 26)
    Legacy identifiers: 1994-03 to 1994-42
    Locations include: Kew, Southall, Brick Lane, London; Scarborough, North Yorks; Bradford, West Yorkshire; Birmingham, West Midlands; Leicester. Color.
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 1997; 1 folder (Box 26)
    Legacy identifier: 1997-06
    Images were taken in London. Color.
  - U.K.: Non-Stadiums, 2017; 4 folders (Box 26)
    Legacy identifiers: 2017-01 to 2017-04
    Location: Bethnal Green, London. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1990; 10 folders (Box 27)
    Legacy identifiers: 1990-1628 to 1990-1637
    Locations include: Pawtucket, RI; Erie, PA; Indianapolis, IN; Burlington, Davenport, IA; Rochester, NY. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1991; 40 folders (Box 27)
    Legacy identifiers: 1991-1782 to 1991-1825
    Locations include: Greensboro, Fayetteville, Durham, Kinston, and Asheville, NC; Fort Mill, Spartanburg, and Charleston, SC; Pulaski, VA; Johnson City, TN; Bluefield and Charleston, WV; Rochester, Elmira, Watertown, and Oneonta, NY; Pawtucket, RI. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1992; 45 folders (Box 28)
    Legacy identifiers: 1992-1830 to 1992-1911
    Locations include: Bakersfield, Visalia, Stockton, Salinas, Modesto, and San Jose, CA; Kenosha, WI; Butte, Great Falls, and Helena, MT; Alberta, Canada. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1993; 20 folders (Box 28)
    Legacy identifiers: 1993-1948 to 1993-1962; many with no identifiers
    Locations include: New Haven, CT; South Bend, IN; Everett, Tacoma, Spokane, and Yakima, WA; Eugene, Medford, and Bend, OR; Alberta, Canada. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1994; 7 folders (Box 29)
    Legacy identifiers: 1994-46 to 1994-50
    Locations include: Syracuse, NY; Portland, OR; Burlington, VT. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1995; 6 folders (Box 29)
    Legacy identifiers: 1995-1 to 1995-28
    Locations include: New Haven, CT; Nashua, NH; Little Rock, Pine Bluff, AK. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1996; 27 folders (Box 29)
    Legacy identifiers: 1996-6 to 1996-49
    Locations include: Bismarck, Grand Forks, and Minot, ND; Sioux Falls, SD; St. Paul, Brainerd, and Duluth, MN; Ontario, Canada; Rochester and Syracuse, NY; Jacksonville and Daytona, FL. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 1997; 5 folders (Box 29)
    Legacy identifiers: 1997-01 to 1997-10; 1997-82
    Locations include: Vancouver, B. C.; Waterbury, CT; Lynn, MA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 2000; 2 folders (Box 29)
    Legacy identifier: 2000-27
    Location: Lynchburg, VA. Color.
  - U.S. Stadiums: Minor League, 2007; 1 folder (Box 29)
    Legacy identifier: 2007-81
    Location: Midland, MI. Color.
  - Clubs, 1998; 4 folders (Box 30)
    Legacy identifiers: 1998-34 to 1998-136
    Location: New York, NY. Color.
  - Clubs, 1999; 4 folders (Box 30)
    Legacy identifiers: 1999-66 to 1999-133
    Locations include: New York City and Buffalo, NY; West Lebanon, NH; Danbury, CT. Color.
  - Clubs, 2000; 3 folders (Box 30)
    Legacy identifiers: 2000-34 to 2000-136
  - Clubs, 2001; 4 folders (Box 30)
    Legacy identifiers: 2001-01 to 2001-154
  - Clubs, 2003; 3 folders (Box 30)
    Legacy identifiers: 2003-09 to 2003-70
  - North Dakota, 2000; 3 folders (Box 31)
    Legacy identifiers: 2000-133 to 2000-176
    Locations include: Bagley, Bemidji, Ackeley, Park Rapids, Sebeka, Wadena, Deer Creek, Vining, NY Mills, and Crookston, MN; Bena, Black Duck, Nevis, Grafton, Auburn, Grand Forks, Portland, and Casselton, all in ND. Color.
  - North Dakota, 2001; 4 folders (Box 31)
    Legacy identifiers: 2001-55 to 2001-135
    Locations include: Arvilla, Larimore, Michigan, Thompson, Hatton, Mayville, Stephen, Pisek, Langdon, Kenmore, Velva, Drake, Cooperstown, Fingal, Chaffee, Casselton, Grand Forks, Auburn, Fairmont, Wahpeton, Hankinson, Forman, Kathryn, Sharon, Warsaw, Pisek, Devil's Lake, Cando, Rugby, Minot, Hazen, Washburn, Turtle Lake, Barlow, Edmore, all in ND; as well as Brooten, Glenwood, and Lawry, MN. Color.
  - North Dakota, 2002; 3 folders (Box 31)
    Legacy identifiers: 2002-52 to 2002-89
    Locations include: Delano, Litchfield, Atwater, Benson, Morris, Ortonville, Stewart, Dayneville, Paynesville, Parker's Prairie, Mahnomen, Crookston, Thief River Falls, Fertile, Frazee, and New York Mills, MN; Wahpeton, Wyndmoor, La Moure, Kulm, Lehr, Wishek, Elgin, Hettinger, Craven Corner, and Grand Forks, all in ND; as well as Mobridge, Waubay, and Webster, SD. Color.
  - North Dakota, 2003; 3 folders (Box 31)
    Legacy identifiers: 2003-71 to 2003-98
    Locations include: Grand Forks, Thompson, Rugby, Towner, Minot, Ray, Dickenson, Grassy Butte, Belfield, Marmath, Glen Ullin, Jamestown, Grafton, Hannaford, and Warren, all in ND. Color.
  - North Dakota, 2004; 3 folders (Box 31)
    Legacy identifiers: 2004-02 to 2004-28; 2004-88 to 2004-121
    Locations are all in ND and include: Bismarck, Wilton, Max, Sawyer, Minot, Pisek, Thompson, Devil's Lake, Lakota, Grand Forks, Mayville, Buchanan, Wing, Hurdsfield, Berthold, Tioga, Williston, Epping, Zap, Mandan, Steele, Barlow, and Reynolds. Color.
  - Clubs, 2004; 1 folder (Box 32)
    Legacy identifiers: 2004-32 to 2004-55
  - Clubs, 2005; 1 folder (Box 32)
    Legacy identifiers: 2005-39 to 2005-48
  - Clubs, 2007; 2 folders (Box 32)
    Legacy identifiers: 2007-01 to 2007-29; 2007-140 to 2007-152
  - Clubs, 2008; 1 folder (Box 32)
    Legacy identifiers: 2008-14 to 2008-22; 2008-42 to 2008-51
  - Clubs, 2009; 1 folder (Box 32)
    Legacy identifiers: 2009-105 to 2009-143
  - Clubs, 2011; 1 folder (Box 32)
    Legacy identifiers: 2011-100 to 2011-124
  - Clubs, 2014; 1 folder (Box 32)
    Legacy identifiers: 2014-01 to 2014-52
  - Clubs, 2017-2018; 1 folder (Box 32)
    Legacy identifiers: 2017-70 to 2017-78; 2018-01 to 2018-07
  - Mexico, 2004; 1 folder (Box 33)
    Legacy identifiers: 2004-61 to 2004-87
    Locations include: Herradora; Atzacoalco; Taxco; Acapulco; Antigua Argentina; Naucalpan. Color.
  - Mexico, 2005; 4 folders (Box 33)
    Legacy identifiers: 2005-02 to 2005-38; 2005-49 to 2005-95
    Locations include: Noche Buena; Periodista; Mexico City; Guanajuato State; Michoacan State; Antigua Argentina; Naucalpan; Herradura; Independencia; Polanca; Hulilcan. Color.
  - Mexico, 2006; 4 folders (Box 33)
    Legacy identifiers: 2006-01 to 2006-89
    Locations include: Mexico City; Talpan; Coyoacan; Tepito; Herradura; Pedregal; Polanco; Tlaltenango. Color.
  - Mexico, 2007; 3 folders
    Legacy identifiers: 2007-31 to 2007-68; 2007-153 to 2007-191
    Locations include: El Huizachal; San Antonio; Coyoacan; Mexico City; Lomas Hipodromo; Las Palmas; Buenavista; Pedregal; Santa Fe; San Angel; Polanco; Centro Historico; Antigua Argentina. Color.
  - Mexico, 2011; 3 folders (Box 34)
    Legacy identifiers: 2011-31 to 2011-74
    Most images are of taco stands, with some restaurants. Locations include: Puebla; Mexico City; Bosque de Chapultepec; Pedregal. Color.
  - Mexico, 2012; 2 folders (Box 34)
    Legacy identifiers: 2012-165 to 2012-201
    Most images are of taco stands, with some restaurants. Locations include: Vera Cruz; Herrador. Color.
  - Mexico, 2013; singles; 2 folders (Box 34)
    Legacy identifiers: 2013-04 to 2013-32
    Most images are of taco stands, with some restaurants. Locations include: Mixcoac; San Angel; Coyoacan; San Antonio; Pedregal; Naucalpan; Dondes; Tlalpan. Color.
  - Argentina/ Uruguay: Carritos, 2016; 2 folders (Box 35)
    Legacy identifiers: 2016-24 to 2016-69
    All are images from the "Carritos" series. Locations include: Concepción del Uruguay and Entre Ríos, Argentina; Salto, Bella Unión, Tomás Gomensoro, Artigas, Rivera, Tanquera, Tacuarembó, Paso de Toros, Durazno and Mercedes, Uruguay. Color.
  - Argentina/ Uruguay: Carritos, 2017; 2 folders (Box 35)
    Legacy identifiers: 2017-13 to 2017-39
    All are images from the "Carritos" series. Locations include: Gualeguaychú, Argentina; Mercedes, Constancia, Tacuarembó, Ansina, Melo, Treinta Y Tres, Solís, San Jacinto, and Montevideo, Uruguay. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 2007; 3 folders (Box 36)
    Legacy identifiers: 2007-112 to 2007-152; 2007-154 to 2007-169
    Locations include: Boca, Palermo, Recoleta, Bajo Flores, San Telmo, La Paternal, Barracas, San Isidro, Recoleta, and San Telmo, Buenos Aires; Santa Fe, Guadalupe, and Esperanza, Santa Fe Province. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay, 2008; 3 folders (Box 36)
    Legacy identifiers: 2008-98 to 2008-152
    Locations include: North Perdices, Entre Rios, Corrientes, Formosa, Chaco, and San Martin, Argentina. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay: Carritos, 2009; 3 folders (Box 36)
    Legacy identifiers: 2009-46 to 2009-103
    Almost all are images from the "Carritos" series. Locations include: Montevideo, Santa Lucia, and Mercedes, Uruguay. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay: Carritos, 2010; 3 folders (Box 36)
    Legacy identifiers: 2010-18 to 2010-77
    All are images from the "Carritos" series. Locations include: Palermo Woods, Costanera Sur, Costanera Norte, and Mercedes, Buenos Aires; Sacramento, Argentina; Rosario, Tarariras, Cardona, Trinidad, Sarandí Grande, Florida, Canelones, Montevideo, Pando, and Ecilda Paullier, Uruguay. Color.
  - Argentina / Uruguay: Carritos, 2012; 3 folders (Box 36)
    Legacy identifiers: 2012-44 to 2012-100
    All are images from the "Carritos" series. Locations include: Santa Fe Province and Entre Rios, Argentina; Mercedes, San Carlos, Montevideo, Santa Lucia, Trinidad, Young, and Paysandu, Uruguay. Color.
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2008; singles; 1 folder (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2008-23 to 2008-41
    Images from Los Angeles, CA. Color.
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2009; 1 folder (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2009-01 to 2009-45
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2010; 1 folder (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2010-04 to 2010-16
    Images taken in San Jose, Oakland, Tulare, and Stockton, CA. Color.
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2011; 1 folder (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2011-17 to 2011-29; 2011-80 to 2011-81; 2011-91 to 2011-139
    Locations include: Chatsworth, Los Angeles, Lodi, Woodland, and Vallejo, CA; Cut Off, and Houma, LA; Port Arthur, and Mauriceville, TX; Hillsborough, NC; Philadelphia, PA. Color.
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2012; 2 folders (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2012-01 to 2012-43; 2012-138 to 2012-163; 2012-208 to 2012-210
    Locations include: Dixon, Vallejo, Napa, Sonoma, Santa Rosa, Petaluma, San Bruno, Redwood City, Selma, Delano, Bakersfield, Lamont, Los Angeles, Chula Vista, Rialto, and Burlington, CA; Durham, Chapel Hill, Cary, High Point, Burlington, and Raleigh, NC; Portland, Olympia, and Beaverton, OR; Seattle, Tacoma, and Olympia, WA. Color.
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2013; 1 folder (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2013-01 to 2013-02; 2013-34 to 2013-52
    Locations include: London; Los Angeles, CA; Philadelphia and Plymouth Meeting, PA; High Point, NC. Color.
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2014; 1 folder (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2014-12 to 2014-57; 2014-69, 2014-79; 2014-121 to 2014-125
    Locations include: Houston, Austin, TX; Harrisonburg, VA; Louisville, KY; Allentown, PA; New Haven, CT. Color.
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2015; 2 folders (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2015-01 to 2015-36; 2015-A, 2015-B
    Locations include: New Haven, CT; Philadelphia, PA; Cambridge, Boston, and Arlington, MA; Durham, Morrisville, Carrboro, and Hillsborough, NC; San Antonio, Houston, TX. Color.
  - U.S. Taco Trucks, 2017; 1 folder (Box 37)
    Legacy identifiers: 2016-01 to 2016-07; 2017-47
    Locations include: Houston, Austin, TX; Louisville, KY. Color.
  - U.S. Road / BBQ, 2012; 2 folders (Box 38)
    Legacy identifiers: 2012-26 to 2012-38; 2012-202 to 2012-206
    Locations include: Ontario, California; Mebane, Durham, Lexington, and China Grove, NC; Hemingway and Loris, SC; Elgin and Aurora, IL. Includes images of Sears houses. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2013; 1 folder (Box 38)
    Legacy identifiers: 2013-46; 2013-54 to 2013-56
    Locations: Philadelphia, PA; Hillsborough, and Durham, NC. Color.
  - U.S. Road / BBQ, 2014; 3 folders (Box 38)
    Legacy identifiers: 2014-53 to 2014-118
    Locations include: First folder houses images from Harrisonburg, Staunton, Christiansburg, Wytheville, and Pennington Gap, VA; Cumberland, Hyden, and Louisville, KY; Georgetown, IN; Cincinnati, OH; Bridgeport, WV; Bedford and Bethlehem, PA. Two folders contain many images of Jackson Hole, WY. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2015; 1 folder (Box 38)
    Legacy identifiers: 2015-20; 2015-37
    Locations: Haw River, NC; Houston, TX. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2016; 1 folder (Box 38)
    Legacy identifiers: 2016-78 to 2016-80
    Location: Salem, NH. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2017; 1 folder (Box 38)
    Legacy identifiers: 2017-05 to 2017-12; 2012-40 to 2017-81
    Locations include: McClellanville, SC; Saugus, MA; Nashville, Lebanon, Juliet, and Bristol, TN; Louisville, KY; Cherokee, Black Mountain, and Hickory, NC; Arlington, Lynchburg, Greenville, and Harrisonburg, VA; Plains, Wilkes Barre, Blakely, and Nanticoke, PA. Color.
  - U.S. Road, 2018; 1 folder (Box 38)
    Legacy identifiers: 2018-08, 2018-10
    Locations include: Nanticoke and Bethlehem, PA. Color.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1985; 1 folder (Box 39)
    Location: Boston Garden. Color.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1986; 1 folder (Box 39)
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1992; 3 folders (Box 39)
    Legacy identifiers: 1992-1935; 1992-1935A; 1992-1937
    Location: Harvard Stadium. Color.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1995; 2 folders (Box 39)
    Location: Fleet Center. Color.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1995; 1 folder (Box 39)
    Location: Fleet Center. Color 4x5 inch negatives. Note states the images are by Tony Rinaldo.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1996; 3 folders (Box 39)
    Legacy identifiers: 1996-01, 1996-03, 1996-04
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1997; 3 folders (Box 39)
    Locations include: Alumni Field, Lowell, and Fraser Field, Lynn MA; Fenway Park, Boston (2 panel sets). Color.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1998; 2 folders (Box 39)
    Legacy identifiers: 1998-35; 1998-108
    Location: Matthew's Stadium, Boston; Foxboro Stadium, Foxboro, MA. Color.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 1999; 1 folder (Box 39)
    Legacy identifiers: 1999-134
    Location: Fenway Park. Color.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 2002; 1 folder (Box 39)
    Legacy identifiers: 2002-95
    Location: Gillette Stadium, Foxborough, MA. Color.
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 2005; 1 folder (Box 39)
    Legacy identifiers: 2005-101 to 2005-104
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 2010; 1 folders (Box 39)
  - Boston Area Stadiums, 2011; 1 folder (Box 39)
    Legacy identifier: 2011-30
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1985; 1 folder (Box 40)
    Strawberries [Records and Tapes] Job, Cambridge, MA. Storefront. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1986; 2 folders (Box 40)
    Legacy identifiers: 1986-1172 to 1986-1179
    Rhode Island School of Design, Providence, RI. Various locations. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1992; 4 folders (Box 40)
    Legacy identifiers: 1192-1849 to 1992-1930; some with no identifiers
    Yale Law School, New Haven, CT. Various locations. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1993; 3 folders (Box 40)
    Legacy identifiers: 1993-1/15 to 1993-14/15; 1993-1/20 to 1993-4/20, 1993 20/20; 1993-1893 to 1993-1925; 1993-1930 to 1993-1946
    Albuquerque House; Talbot House, Rockport, ME; MIT, Cambridge, MA. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1994; 2 folders (Box 40)
    Boston Garden, Boston, MA. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1996; 2 folders (Box 40)
    Legacy identifiers: 1996-38 to 1996-45 (Palmer House); others not identified
    School of the Museum of Fine Art (SMFA) - Museum School, Boston, MA; Palmer House, Edinburgh, Scotland. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1997; 2 folders (Box 40)
    Legacy identifiers: 1997-3 to 1997-9
    Garden Museum, Lambeth, London; Logan Airport Children's Museum, Boston. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1998; 2 folders (Box 40)
    Boston College; Andover Annual Report, Andover, MA. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1998; 1 folder (Box 41)
    MIT, Cambridge, MA. Various locations. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1998; 1 folder (Box 41)
    NY Times Design Issue, Rashid & Mandelbaum, Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1999; 1 folder (Box 41)
    Legacy identifiers: 1999-1/9 to 9/9
    MIT "Infinite Corridors" series, Cambridge, MA. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 1999; 1 folder (Box 41)
    Legacy identifiers: 1999-94, 1994-95
    Federal Reserve Building façade, New York, NY. Color.
  - Jobs and Commissions, 2004; 1 folder (Box 41)
    Legacy identifiers: 2004-56 to 2004-59